I know what Castro you see you hold on
Hi
Joe
Okay
Thank you natural nuts guru. Thank you
Kind of get down like people just the mad me. I'm not doing anything, right?
Well, she I mean she said it on my show
She said oh, yeah, so now it's so that what she said it turns into my whatever
And she didn't comment in the chat if she could have said something in the chat
But she wants to go talk to me about it
Wasn't like oh and intrusive thoughts. I've had intrusive thoughts, too
I mean, it's like not the biggest deal you can deal with intrusive thoughts the thing was it's like
She said it in a way that was like disturbing. I don't know
I knew I know it's gonna be a hate that my ears are burning. That's how I feel it
It goes like this negative energy coming toward me right now
Yeah, I know who it is. I mean, it's the same person that has always been but I mean one of them
But if you try to do it twice already, then he just an n-word bomb me
Then what's like the people like mass flagging? No
Hey, Dougie Doug
Clean shave and I am
I had a little shave today
I'm okay. I'm okay. It's a little bit stressful, you know as usual and
I do I do feel some love right now, but thank you chat and everything. Thank you for I
Was like, oh, don't don't make people feel sorry for you. That's I'm not trying to make people feel sorry for me
I'm just myself
You know
Second I take it but I take it per I think it is if you're basically as if you're calling me the n word
Which is fine. I don't think means they can call me the n word or anything, but that's how I take it. I mean, that's so it is like hurtful
Psycho drama
I feel like just like crawling under a rock tonight, so
Cold
What's up? It's like I'm feeling a little bit cold. I feel like a lot of like negative energy
and the hatred
I kind of felt now I feel like it's getting more and it's like
I don't know how long I'll last here but a serious attack again. He told me
People are like probably literally sitting like all fishing like flag flag flag flag flag my channel
They're not even doing anything right?
You're not the best data to come on.
I want you guys to have fun.
Chill.
Now I'm in the same room
Thanks J-Dog. Well, I don't know. I don't know. It's
It's the glasses style. Yeah, maybe I
Say if that's what that's what looks different
It was it's like I've never really mad at people I sometimes they like old lash out
So they were like, you know me sometimes for attention, I guess or I don't know
so they can like
Can I see if they likes care still and it's like then they come back and they're like they're like hateful
I'm really sorry guys. I don't want to be a downer tonight
You feel like it's over
Love you guys